//FUNCTIONS AND VARIABLES
//============================================
var triviaQuestions = [{
	question: "What is the name of the Mega Man X's creator?",
	answerList: ["Dr. Wily", "Dr. Light", "Dr. Cossack", "Dr. Hikari"],
	answer: 1
},{
	question: "In Mega Man X2, which boss stage is reused for the final fight against Sigma?",
	answerList: ["Magna Centipede", "Wire Sponge", "Overdrive Ostrich", "Crystal Snail"],
	answer: 0
},{
	question: "In Mega Man X3, what is the maximum number of upgrade capsules that can be used per playthrough?",
	answerList: ["5", "4", "9", "6"],
	answer: 0
},{
	question: "In Mega Man X4, what is the name of the all-reploid army?",
	answerList: ["The Resistance", "The Guardians", "Repliforce", "X-Hunters"],
	answer: 2
},{
	question: "In English version of Mega Man X5, all 8 main bosses named after members of which rockband? ",
	answerList: ["Aerosmith", "The Beatles", "Nirvana", "Guns'N'Roses"],
	answer: 3
},{
	question: "In Mega Man X6, the 8 main bosses can be skipped altogether by beating which hidden boss?",
	answerList: ["High Max", "Vile", "Serges", "Byte"],
	answer: 0
},{
	question: "In Mega Man X7, what are the only two characters you can use in the beginning?",
	answerList: ["X and Zero", "Zero and Axl", "Layer and Zero", "Axl and Alia"],
	answer: 1
},{
	question: "Upon certain conditions, what classic Mega Man boss can be fought in Mega Man X8?",
	answerList: ["Bass", "Air Man", "Cut Man", "Duo"],
	answer: 2
},{
	question: "Maverick Hunter?",
	answerList: ["Amy Poehler", "Phyllis Smith", "Mindy Kaling", "Phyllis Vance"],
	answer: 1
},{
	question: "Command Mission",
	answerList: ["Hopper", "Woody", "Marlin", "Buzz Lightyear"],
	answer: 3
},
];




//when button clicked
	//html changes to 8 MC questions and submit button
	$('#start').click()
	//timer starts



//when answer is clicked
	//record answer as right or wrong for question

//if time runs out OR submit button is clicked
	//change html to results
		//correct answers
		//incorrect answers
		// unanswered questions
	//add a restart button (if you can)